licious.in 2019-12-27

# Privacy Policy

_Disclaimer: The Company can modify this Policy unilaterally at any time without notice. Modification may be necessary, among other reasons, to maintain compliance with applicable laws and regulations or accommodate organizational changes within the Company._

By ordering from Licious.in, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. As we continue to develop our website and the app, if any, and employ emerging technologies to improve the services we provide, this Privacy Policy may change. We encourage you to refer to this Privacy Policy to understand our current privacy policy. 

By mere use of the Website, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with the Privacy Policy. Privacy Policy is deemed to be incorporated into and is subject to the Terms of Service Agreement. By using the services or by otherwise giving us your information, you will be deemed to have read, understood and agreed to the practices and policies outlined in this privacy policy and agree to be bound by the privacy policy. You hereby consent to our collection, use and sharing, disclosure of your information as described in this privacy policy. We reserve the right to change, modify, add or delete portions of the terms of this privacy policy, at our sole discretion, at any time. If you do not agree with this privacy policy at any time, do not use any of the services or give us any of your information. if you use the services on behalf of someone else (such as your child) or an entity (such as your employer), you represent that you are authorised by such individual or entity to (i) accept this privacy policy on such individual’s or entity’s behalf, and (ii) consent on behalf of such individual or entity to our collection, use and disclosure of such individual’s or entity’s information as described in this privacy policy. 

Delightful Gourmet Private Limited (“ **Company** ” or “ **Licious** ”) has created this privacy policy (“ **Privacy Policy** ” or “ **Policy** ”) to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting information you submit. We understand that you care about how information about you is used. We are committed to protecting your privacy and your personal information. This also applies to services and products offered by Licious, as well as any other applications, content or features that we may from time to time offer on our website or the app. 

This Privacy Policy describes how the Company manages personal information collected, received, or maintained. We collect information pertaining to you which may be classified as personal information and sensitive personal data or information and all other types of information through our website, other online services and other modes. 

We take utmost care to protect your privacy. This Privacy Policy pertains to the different means of how we collect your information and describes how your personal information is stored and treated. 

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy,

The term “ **PI** ” (Personal Information) means any personal information that relates to a natural person which, either directly or indirectly, in combination with other information available or likely to be available is capable of identifying such person. 

The terms “ **SPI** ” (Sensitive Personal Information) of a person means such personal information which consists of information relating to (i) password; (ii) financial information such as bank account or credit card or debit card or other payment instrument details; (iii) physical, physiological and mental health condition; (iv) sexual orientation; (v) medical records and history; (vi) biometric information; (vii) any detail relating to the above shared with us for providing service; and (viii) any of the information received under above clauses for processing: provided that any information that is freely available or accessible in public domain or furnished under the Right to Information Act, 2005 or any other law for the time being in force shall not be regarded as SPI. 

Should you have any grievances about the processing of your personal information, you may contact Varun Sadana with respect to Data Protection and Privacy related complaints at varun@licious.com. All email messages sent to and from www.licious.in may be monitored with the objective of ensuring compliance with internal policies and to protect our business.
